Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874/1875; phaedra1473 (Box 63)
  KG11366.469
  F40
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874/1875; phaedra1474 (Box 63)
  KG11366.470
  F41
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874/1875; phaedra1475 (Box 63)
  KG11366.471
  F42
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874/1875; phaedra1476 (Box 63)
  KG11366.472
  F43
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874/1875; phaedra1477 (Box 63)
  KG11366.473
  F44
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874/1875; phaedra1478 (Box 63)
  KG11366.474
  F45
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874/1875; phaedra1479 (Box 63)
  KG11366.475
  F46
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874/1875; phaedra1480 (Box 63)
  KG11366.476
  F47
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1876/1877; phaedra1481 (Box 63)
  KG11366.477
  F48
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1876/1877; phaedra1482 (Box 63)
  KG11366.478
  F49
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1876/1877; phaedra1483 (Box 63)
  KG11366.479
  F50
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1876/1877; phaedra1484 (Box 63)
  KG11366.480
  F51
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1876/1877; phaedra1485 (Box 63)
  KG11366.481
  F52
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1876/1877; phaedra1486 (Box 63)
  KG11366.482
  F53
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1877; phaedra1487 (Box 63)
  KG11366.483
  F54
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1877; phaedra1488 (Box 63)
  KG11366.484
  F55
- Maskelyne Fundamentals, 1877; phaedra1489 (Box 63)
  KG11366.485
  F56
- Meridian Circle, 1875; phaedra1490 (Box 63)
  KG11366.486
- Maskelyne Fundamentals, 1877; phaedra1491 (Box 63)
  KG11366.487
  F57
- Fundamental Stars, 1878; phaedra1492 (Box 63)
  KG11366.488
  F59
- Fundamental Stars, 1878; phaedra1493 (Box 63)
  KG11366.489
  F60
- Fundamental Stars, 1878; phaedra1494 (Box 63)
  KG11366.490
  F61
- Fundamental Stars, 1878; phaedra1495 (Box 64)
  KG11366.491
  F62
- Coast Survey Catalog, 1878; phaedra1496 (Box 64)
  KG11366.492
  F63
- Coast Survey Catalog, 1878; phaedra1497 (Box 64)
  KG11366.493
  F64
- Coast Survey Catalog, 1878; phaedra1498 (Box 64)
  KG11366.494
  F65
- Miscellaneous Stars, 1878; phaedra1499 (Box 64)
  KG11366.495
  F66
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1878; phaedra1500 (Box 64)
  KG11366.496
  F67
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1879; phaedra1501 (Box 64)
  KG11366.497
  F68
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1879; phaedra1502 (Box 64)
  KG11366.498
  F69
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1879; phaedra1503 (Box 64)
  KG11366.499
  F70
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1879; phaedra1504 (Box 64)
  KG11366.500
  F71
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1879; phaedra1505 (Box 64)
  KG11366.501
  F72
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1879; phaedra1506 (Box 64)
  KG11366.502
  F73
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1879; phaedra1507 (Box 64)
  KG11366.503
  F74
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; phaedra1508 (Box 64)
  KG11366.504
  F75
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; phaedra1509 (Box 64)
  KG11366.505
  F76
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; phaedra1510 (Box 64)
  KG11366.506
  F77
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; phaedra1511 (Box 64)
  KG11366.507
  F78
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; phaedra1512 (Box 64)
  KG11366.508
  F79
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; phaedra1513 (Box 64)
  KG11366.509
  F80
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; phaedra1514 (Box 64)
  KG11366.510
  F81
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; phaedra1515 (Box 64)
  KG11366.511
  F82
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1881; phaedra1516 (Box 64)
  KG11366.512
  F83
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1881; phaedra1517 (Box 64)
  KG11366.513
  F84
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1881-04-21/1881-08-21; phaedra1518 (Box 65)
  KG11366.514
  F85
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1881-02-29/1883-03-23; phaedra1519 (Box 65)
  KG11366.515
  F90
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1881-02-08/1883-02-28; phaedra1520 (Box 65)
  KG11366.516
  F89
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1881-10-27/1882-01-10; phaedra1521 (Box 65)
  KG11366.517
  F88
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1881-09-25/1881-10-27; phaedra1522 (Box 65)
  KG11366.518
  F87
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1881-08-21/1881-09-25; phaedra1523 (Box 65)
  KG11366.519
  F86
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1879-02-12/1879-10-01; phaedra1524 (Box 65)
  KG11366.520
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1879-10-04/1880-01-02; phaedra1525 (Box 65)
  KG11366.521
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1880-09-01/1881-02-10; phaedra1526 (Box 65)
  KG11366.522
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1881-02-10/1881-09-20; phaedra1527 (Box 65)
  KG11366.523
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1881-09-21/1883-01-08; phaedra1528 (Box 65)
  KG11366.524
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1883-02-07/1883-09-06; phaedra1529 (Box 65)
  KG11366.525
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1883-09-06/1884-01-03; phaedra1530 (Box 65)
  KG11366.526
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1884-01-03/1884-09-09; phaedra1531 (Box 65)
  KG11366.527
  E9
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1885-04-30/1886-02-02; phaedra1532 (Box 65)
  KG11366.528
  E10
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1870-11-01/1870-12-22; phaedra1533 (Box 65)
  KG11366.529
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1870-12-26/1871-02-21; phaedra1534 (Box 65)
  KG11366.530
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1871-02-11/1871-04-05; phaedra1535 (Box 65)
  KG11366.531
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1871-04-05/1871-05-24; phaedra1536 (Box 65)
  KG11366.532
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1871-05-25/1871-07-03; phaedra1537 (Box 65)
  KG11366.533
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1871-07-05/1871-09-01; phaedra1538 (Box 65)
  KG11366.534
- Zone Circle Readings, 1871; phaedra1539 (Box 65)
  KG11366.535
  C6'
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1871-09-02/1871-11-02; phaedra1540 (Box 65)
  KG11366.536
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1871-11-06/1872-03-11; phaedra1541 (Box 65)
  KG11366.537
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1872-03-14/1872-10-02; phaedra1542 (Box 65)
  KG11366.538
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1872-10-03/1873-03-05; phaedra1543 (Box 65)
  KG11366.539
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1873-03-06/1873-08-11; phaedra1544 (Box 65)
  KG11366.540
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1873-10-05/1874-01-20; phaedra1545 (Box 65)
  KG11366.541
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1874-01-17/1874-04-22; phaedra1546 (Box 66)
  KG11366.542
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1874-05-07/1874-07-28; phaedra1547 (Box 66)
  KG11366.543
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1874-07-30/1874-10-19; phaedra1548 (Box 66)
  KG11366.544
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1874-10-20/1875-01-05; phaedra1549 (Box 66)
  KG11366.545
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1875-01-10/1875-03-30; phaedra1550 (Box 66)
  KG11366.546
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1875-03-31/1875-06-28; phaedra1551 (Box 66)
  KG11366.547
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1875-08-07/1875-11-22; phaedra1552 (Box 66)
  KG11366.548
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1875-11-08/1876-05-30; phaedra1553 (Box 66)
  KG11366.549
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1876-08-06/1876-12-23; phaedra1554 (Box 66)
  KG11366.550
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1876-12-24/1877-02-14; phaedra1555 (Box 66)
  KG11366.551
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1878-09-15/1879-01-26; phaedra1556 (Box 66)
  KG11366.552
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1877-12-17/1878-09-14; phaedra1557 (Box 66)
  KG11366.553
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1877-02-14/1877-10-01; phaedra1558 (Box 66)
  KG11366.554
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1879-02-15/1879-08-20; phaedra1559 (Box 66)
  KG11366.555
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1879-08-24/1880-01-01; phaedra1560 (Box 66)
  KG11366.556
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1880-03-01/1880-07-26; phaedra1561 (Box 66)
  KG11366.557
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1880-07-28/1881-01-12; phaedra1562 (Box 66)
  KG11366.558
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1881-01-15/1881-07-15; phaedra1563 (Box 66)
  KG11366.559
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1881-07-17/1883-03-21; phaedra1564 (Box 66)
  KG11366.560
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1883-03-22/1883-11-11; phaedra1565 (Box 66)
  KG11366.561
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1883-11-12/1884-04-11; phaedra1566 (Box 66)
  KG11366.562
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1870-11-10/1870-12-13; phaedra1567 (Box 66)
  KG11366.563
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1870-12-18/1871-01-17; phaedra1568 (Box 66)
  KG11366.564
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871-01-17/1871-03-05; phaedra1569 (Box 66)
  KG11366.565
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871-03-07/1871-04-17; phaedra1570 (Box 66)
  KG11366.566
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871-04-17/1871-05-23; phaedra1571 (Box 66)
  KG11366.567
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871-05-18/1871-06-12; phaedra1572 (Box 66)
  KG11366.568
  C6
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871-06-06/1871-06-30; phaedra1573 (Box 66)
  KG11366.569
  C7
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871-06-30/1871-07-27; phaedra1574 (Box 66)
  KG11366.570
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871-08-02/1871-08-28; phaedra1575 (Box 67)
  KG11366.571
  William A. Rogers, Henry Gannett, Augustus McConnel
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871-08-28/1871-09-14; phaedra1576 (Box 67)
  KG11366.572
  Augustus McConnel, William A. Rogers, Henry Gannett
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871-09-18/1871-11-02; phaedra1577 (Box 67)
  KG11366.573
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871-11-02/1871-12-12; phaedra1578 (Box 67)
  KG11366.574
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871-12-20/1872-03-11; phaedra1579 (Box 67)
  KG11366.575
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1872-02-11/1872-02-14; phaedra1580 (Box 67)
  KG11366.576
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1872-02-11/1873-01-01; phaedra1581 (Box 67)
  KG11366.577
  C15
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1873-01-01/1873-02-24; phaedra1582 (Box 67)
  KG11366.578
  C16
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1873-02-24/1873-04-27; phaedra1583 (Box 67)
  KG11366.579
  C17
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1873-04-27/1874-02-10; phaedra1584 (Box 67)
  KG11366.580
  C18
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1873-10-05/1873-11-19; phaedra1585 (Box 67)
  KG11366.581
  C19
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1873-11-18/1874-02-10; phaedra1586 (Box 67)
  KG11366.582
  C20
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874-02-11/1874-04-06; phaedra1587 (Box 67)
  KG11366.583
  C21
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874-04-02/1874-06-10; phaedra1588 (Box 67)
  KG11366.584
  C22
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874-06-18/1874-08-22; phaedra1589 (Box 67)
  KG11366.585
  C23
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874-08-06/1874-09-14; phaedra1590 (Box 67)
  KG11366.586
  C24
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874-09-12/1874-10-26; phaedra1591 (Box 67)
  KG11366.587
  C25
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874-10-22/1874-11-26; phaedra1592 (Box 67)
  KG11366.588
  C26
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874-11-24/1875-01-30; phaedra1593 (Box 67)
  KG11366.589
  C27
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1875-01-27/1875-03-25; phaedra1594 (Box 67)
  KG11366.590
  C28
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1875-03-23/1875-04-22; phaedra1595 (Box 67)
  KG11366.591
  C29
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1875-04-24/1875-06-21; phaedra1596 (Box 67)
  KG11366.592
  C30
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1875-06-20/1875-09-14; phaedra1597 (Box 67)
  KG11366.593
  C31
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1875-09-08/1875-11-22; phaedra1598 (Box 67)
  KG11366.594
  C32
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1875-11-08/1876-01-20; phaedra1599 (Box 67)
  KG11366.595
  C33
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1876-01-26/1876-08-26; phaedra1600 (Box 67)
  KG11366.596
  C34
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1876-08-26/1876-10-24; phaedra1601 (Box 67)
  KG11366.597
  C35
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1876-10-29/1877-01-14; phaedra1602 (Box 67)
  KG11366.598
  C36
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1877-01-20/1877-04-23; phaedra1603 (Box 67)
  KG11366.599
  C37
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1877-04-26/1877-08-16; phaedra1604 (Box 67)
  KG11366.600
  C38
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1877; phaedra1605 (Box 68)
  KG11366.601
  C39
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1877; phaedra1606 (Box 68)
  KG11366.602
  C40
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1877/1878; phaedra1607 (Box 68)
  KG11366.603
  C41
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1878; phaedra1608 (Box 68)
  KG11366.604
  C42
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1878/1879; phaedra1609 (Box 68)
  KG11366.605
  C43
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1883; phaedra1610 (Box 68)
  KG11366.606
  C44
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1883/1884; phaedra1611 (Box 68)
  KG11366.607
  C45
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1884; phaedra1612 (Box 68)
  KG11366.608
  C46
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1884/1885; phaedra1613 (Box 68)
  KG11366.609
  C47
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1885; phaedra1614 (Box 68)
  KG11366.610
  C48
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1885; phaedra1615 (Box 68)
  KG11366.611
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1883; phaedra1616 (Box 68)
  KG11366.612
  F91
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1883; phaedra1617 (Box 68)
  KG11366.613
  F92
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1883/1884; phaedra1618 (Box 68)
  KG11366.614
  F96
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1884; phaedra1619 (Box 68)
  KG11366.615
  F97
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1885; phaedra1620 (Box 68)
  KG11366.616
  F98
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1885; phaedra1621 (Box 68)
  KG11366.617
  F99
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1885/1886; phaedra1622 (Box 68)
  KG11366.618
  F100
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1885; phaedra1623 (Box 68)
  KG11366.619
  F101
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1885; phaedra1624 (Box 68)
  KG11366.620
  F102
- Collection of Results in Order of Dates, 1879/1881; phaedra1625 (Box 68)
  KG11366.621
- Readings of the Sun, 1879; phaedra1626 (Box 68)
  KG11366.622
- Observations of the Sun, 1879; phaedra1627 (Box 68)
  KG11366.623
  Sidney Wetmore, Arville Walker
- Error of Frodsham 1327, 1903/1904; phaedra1628 (Box 69)
  KG11366.624
  Marion F. Michaelis, William W. White, John A. Dunne
- Error of Frodsham 1328, 1904/1905; phaedra1629 (Box 69)
  KG11366.625
- Error of Frodsham 1329, 1905; phaedra1630 (Box 69)
  KG11366.626
- Error of Frodsham 1330, 1905/1906; phaedra1631 (Box 69)
  KG11366.627
  Marion F. Michaelis, William W. White
- Error of Frodsham 1331, 1906/1907; phaedra1632 (Box 69)
  KG11366.628
  John A. Dunne, William W. White
- Error of Frodsham 1332, 1907/1908; phaedra1633 (Box 69)
  KG11366.629
  William W. White, John A. Dunne
- Error of Frodsham 1333, 1908; phaedra1634 (Box 69)
  KG11366.630
- Error of Frodsham 1334, 1901; phaedra1635 (Box 69)
  KG11366.631
  John A. Dunne, Marion F. Michaelis, Wilard P. Gerrish, Arthur Searle
- Error of Frodsham 1335, 1899/1900; phaedra1636 (Box 69)
  KG11366.632
- Error of Frodsham 1336, 1896/1898; phaedra1637 (Box 69)
  KG11366.633
  John A. Dunne, Arthur Searle
- Error of Frodsham 1337, 1902/1903; phaedra1638 (Box 69)
  KG11366.634
- Chronograph Record, 1879; phaedra1639 (Box 69)
  KG11366.635
  J20
- Chronograph Record, 1871; phaedra1640 (Box 69)
  KG11366.636
  J3
  See KG11366.871 and KG11366.872 for J1 and J2
- Chronograph Record, 1871; phaedra1641 (Box 69)
  KG11366.637
  J4
- Chronograph Record, 1872; phaedra1642 (Box 69)
  KG11366.638
  J5
- Chronograph Record, 1872; phaedra1643 (Box 69)
  KG11366.639
  J6
- Chronograph Record, 1872/1873; phaedra1644 (Box 69)
  KG11366.640
  J7
- Chronograph Record, 1873; phaedra1645 (Box 69)
  KG11366.641
  J8
- Chronograph Record, 1873/1874; phaedra1646 (Box 69)
  KG11366.642
  J9
- Chronograph Record, 1874; phaedra1647 (Box 69)
  KG11366.643
  J10
- Chronograph Record, 1874/1875; phaedra1648 (Box 69)
  KG11366.644
  J11
- Chronograph Record, 1875; phaedra1649 (Box 69)
  KG11366.645
  J12
- Chronograph Record, 1875/1876; phaedra1650 (Box 69)
  KG11366.646
  J13
- Chronograph Record, 1876; phaedra1651 (Box 69)
  KG11366.647
  J14
- Chronograph Record, 1876; phaedra1652 (Box 69)
  KG11366.648
  J15
- Chronograph Record, 1876/1877; phaedra1653 (Box 69)
  KG11366.649
  J16
- Chronograph Record, 1877; phaedra1654 (Box 69)
  KG11366.650
  J17
- Chronograph Record, 1877; phaedra1655 (Box 69)
  KG11366.651
  J18
- Chronograph Record, 1878/1879; phaedra1656 (Box 69)
  KG11366.652
  J19
- Chronograph Record, 1879/1880; phaedra1657 (Box 69)
  KG11366.653
  J21
- Chronograph Record, 1880; phaedra1658 (Box 69)
  KG11366.654
  J22
- Chronograph Record, 1880/1881; phaedra1659 (Box 69)
  KG11366.655
  J24
  William A. Rogers, Wilbur V. Brown
- Chronograph Record, 1881; phaedra1660 (Box 69)
  KG11366.656
  J25
- Chronograph Record, 1881; phaedra1661 (Box 69)
  KG11366.657
  J26
- Chronograph Record, 1881/1882; phaedra1662 (Box 69)
  KG11366.658
  J27
- Chronograph Record, 1883; phaedra1663 (Box 69)
  KG11366.659
  J28
- Chronograph Record, 1883; phaedra1664 (Box 69)
  KG11366.660
  J29
- Chronograph Record, 1883/1884; phaedra1665 (Box 69)
  KG11366.661
  J30
- Reports, Meteorological Notes, 1889/1894; phaedra1666 (Box 70)
  KG11366.662
- Reports, Meteorological Notes, 1886/1888; phaedra1667 (Box 70)
  KG11366.663
- Reports, Meteorological Notes, 1883/1885; phaedra1668 (Box 70)
  KG11366.664
- North Pole Reductions, 1897/1901; phaedra1669 (Box 70)
  KG11366.665
- South Pole Reductions, 1896/1902; phaedra1670 (Box 70)
  KG11366.666
- Variable Stars, Computation, 1895/1901; phaedra1671 (Box 70)
  KG11366.667
  T6
- Tabulation of Observations of Variable Stars, 1903; phaedra1672 (Box 70)
  KG11366.668
- Memoranda and Reminders, 1896; phaedra1673 (Box 70)
  KG11366.669
  T9
- Bright Double Stars, Working Lists, 1880; phaedra1674 (Box 70)
  Date not listed
  KG11366.670
  Ann McCormack, William A. Rogers
- Current Relative and Absolute Estimates, Variable Stars, 1896; phaedra1675 (Box 70)
  KG11366.671
- Variable Stars, Computation, 1899; phaedra1676 (Box 70)
  KG11366.672
- Ephemerides of Variables Stars, 1902; phaedra1677 (Box 70)
  KG11366.673
- Clock Errors, Instrumental Constants, 1871/1872; phaedra1678 (Box 70)
  KG11366.674
- Clock Errors, Polar Catalog, Instrumental Constants, 1872/1873; phaedra1679 (Box 70)
  KG11366.675
- Clock Errors, General Catalog, Instrumental Constants, 1874/1875; phaedra1680 (Box 70)
  KG11366.676
- Clock Errors, General Catalog, Instrumental Constants, 1878/1879; phaedra1681 (Box 70)
  KG11366.677
- Clock Errors, General Catalog, Instrumental Constants, 1883; phaedra1682 (Box 70)
  KG11366.678
- Equator Points, Corrections, 1871/1872; phaedra1683 (Box 70)
  KG11366.679
- Equator Points, Corrections, Flexure Polar Catalog, 1872/1873; phaedra1684 (Box 70)
  KG11366.680
- Equator Points, Corrections, Flexure Constants, 1878; phaedra1685 (Box 70)
  KG11366.681
- Equator Pt. from Obsns of alpha and lambda, 1876; phaedra1686 (Box 70)
  KG11366.682
- Copy of Instrumental Constants 1870-71; Redetermination of deltaT, m h', 1870/1878; phaedra1687 (Box 71)
  KG11366.683
- Instrumental Constants depending on Pulkova Coordinates, 1871/1872; phaedra1688 (Box 71)
  KG11366.684
- Instrumental Constants depending on Pulkova Coordinates, 1872/1873; phaedra1689 (Box 71)
  KG11366.685
- Instrumental Constants depending on Pulkova Coordinates, 1873/1874; phaedra1690 (Box 71)
  KG11366.686
- Instrumental Constants depending on Pulkova Coordinates, 1875; phaedra1691 (Box 71)
  KG11366.687
- Instrumental Constants depending on Pulkova Coordinates, 1876; phaedra1692 (Box 71)
  KG11366.688
- Instrumental Constants depending on Pulkova Coordinates, 1877; phaedra1693 (Box 71)
  KG11366.689
- Instrumental Constants depending on Pulkova Coordinates, 1877; phaedra1694 (Box 71)
  KG11366.690
- Final Values of deltaT, m, reg for reduction of Zone Observations, 1870/1874; phaedra1695 (Box 71)
  KG11366.691
- Final Values of deltaT, m, reg for reduction of Zone Observations, 1874/1878; phaedra1696 (Box 71)
  KG11366.692
- Final Values of n and c for reduction of zone observations, 1872/1876; phaedra1697 (Box 71)
  KG11366.693
- Final Values of n and c for reduction of zone observations, 1876/1878; phaedra1698 (Box 71)
  KG11366.694
- Meridian Circle Constants, A, Star Constants, 1872; phaedra1699 (Box 71)
  KG11366.695
- Instrumental Constants, Star Constants, 1876; phaedra1700 (Box 71)
  KG11366.696
- Inclination of Declination Wires, 1877/1878; phaedra1701 (Box 71)
  KG11366.697
- Zone observations, final reductions, 1855/1875; phaedra1702 (Box 71)
  KG11366.698
  J1
- Zone observations, final reductions, 1855/1875; phaedra1703 (Box 71)
  KG11366.699
  J2
- Zone observations, final reductions, 1855/1875; phaedra1704 (Box 71)
  KG11366.700
- Zone observations, final reductions, 1855/1875; phaedra1705 (Box 71)
  KG11366.701
- Zone observations, final reductions, 1855/1875; phaedra1706 (Box 71)
  KG11366.702
- Zone observations, final reductions, 1883/1885; phaedra1707 (Box 71)
  KG11366.703
- DM list +53 and +54, 1883; phaedra1708 (Box 71)
  KG11366.704
- DM List +50, +51, +52, 1871; phaedra1709 (Box 72)
  KG11366.705
- Thermometer, Barometer Runs, 1873; phaedra1710 (Box 72)
  KG11366.706
  D4
- Thermometer, Barometer Runs, 1875; phaedra1711 (Box 72)
  KG11366.707
  D8
- Thermometer, Barometer Runs, 1875/1876; phaedra1712 (Box 72)
  KG11366.708
  D9
- Thermometer, Barometer Runs, 1876; phaedra1713 (Box 72)
  KG11366.709
  D10
- Planet and Satellite Observations, 1877; phaedra1714 (Box 72)
  KG11366.710
  R14
- Star Observations, 1877; phaedra1715 (Box 72)
  KG11366.711
- Star Observations, 1877/1878; phaedra1716 (Box 72)
  KG11366.712
- Star Observations, 1869; phaedra1717 (Box 72)
  KG11366.713
  R27
- Meteorological Record, 1880/1882; phaedra1718 (Box 72)
  KG11366.714
  R67
- Notes on SMP, 1892; phaedra1719 (Box 72)
  KG11366.715
- Micrometer Level, 1877; phaedra1720 (Box 72)
  KG11366.716
- Reduction of Observations by Schmidt by Reed, 1873; phaedra1721 (Box 72)
  KG11366.717
- Early lists of gaseous neb, stars Pec. Specctra, 1880; phaedra1722 (Box 72)
  KG11366.718
- Discussion of H.A. 24, group MP according to DM, 1895; phaedra1723 (Box 72)
  KG11366.719
- Discussion of H.A. 24, group MP according to DM, 1895; phaedra1724 (Box 72)
  KG11366.720
- Stars and Cluster, Lists with X plates entered, 1899; phaedra1725 (Box 72)
  KG11366.721
- Double Stars, 1907; phaedra1726 (Box 72)
  KG11366.722
- Double Stars, 1895; phaedra1727 (Box 72)
  Date uncertain. Inferred from surrounding materials
  KG11366.723
- Asteroid Zone Book, 1872; phaedra1728 (Box 72)
  KG11366.724
- Eros Book, 1893; phaedra1729 (Box 72)
  KG11366.725
- Eros Book, 1876; phaedra1730 (Box 72)
  KG11366.726
- Zone Stars, 1870; phaedra1731 (Box 72)
  KG11366.727
- Russian Transit, 1873; phaedra1732 (Box 72)
  KG11366.728
  U4
- Zone Circle Recordings, 1870; phaedra1733 (Box 72)
  KG11366.729
  U5
- Zone Circle Recordings, 1870; phaedra1734 (Box 72)
  KG11366.730
  U6
- Zone Circle Recordings, 1871; phaedra1735 (Box 72)
  KG11366.731
  U7
- D.M. List, 1872; phaedra1736 (Box 73)
  KG11366.732
  U10
- Borton's notebook, 1880; phaedra1737 (Box 73)
  KG11366.733
  U
  Martha C. Borton
- Record of work by D.B. Pratt, 1883/1884; phaedra1738 (Box 73)
  KG11366.734
- Stars(zone) needing re-examination of chronograph sheets, 1871; phaedra1739 (Box 73)
  KG11366.735
  U14
- Stars to be re-observed, 1875; phaedra1740 (Box 73)